SAM PETERSON

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

peterson2020@fakeemail.com

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies June 2017 - July 2020

University of Kwazulu-Natal Bachelor of Computer Science Honours July 2020 - Present

SKILL

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

ABOUT ME

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER Google Inc

January 2017 - August 2017

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER Google Inc

January 2017 - August 2017

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal July 2015 - Nov 2017
Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technogies

University of Kwazulu-Natal November 2018
Bachelor of Computer Science Honours